Sean Israel Izuchukwu Madubuike

Contact Details

Address Block A4 Army Housing Scheme Kubwa FCT Abuja, Nigeira

Email israelmadubuike@gmail.com

Phone +234 806 788 9036

Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/in/sean-israel-madubuike-27b97496/

Portfolio https://flozzy.github.io/seanportfoilo/main.html

Objective

A graduate of international Relations and a member of the Nigerian Institute of Management. Aimed with extensive professional skills and experience in surpporting small and medium level companies. Highly motivated, proactive, innovative, and meticulous towards assigned responsibility, and have shown the ability to adapt to new roles.

Skills

Experience in the use and management of computer Software with certification in Desktop Publishing, Proficient in Microsoft office, Expert in project writing and research reports, Effective Management skills and the ability to multi-tesk.

Education

2013 - 2017 Bachelor's Degree: International Relations , ECO.TE.S, Benin Republic :

https://ecotesbenin.org/

Courses include:

- International Economics Relations
- International Political Systems
- Politics of Energy Resources
- Law of Nation
- Foreign Policy and Major Power
- Europe in World Politics
- Race and ethnicity in international relation

2012 - 2013 Diploma in Law (National Diploma), University of Abuja, Abuja, Nigeria :

https://www.uniabuja.edu.ng/

Courses include:

- Company Law
- Commercial Law
- Administrative Law
- Insurance Law
- Communicational Skills
- Moot and Mock Trials
- Legal Research
- Law of evidence
- International Law
- Islamic Law
- Criminal Law

Languages

- English = fluent,
- Igbo = Fluent,

Work Experience

2018 - 2020 Contributions Processing Officer, (Sigma Pensions Limited, Abuja, Nigeria)

- Worked within the department involved in the reconciliation of clients' accounts including due remittances.
- Worked as part of a team responsible for ensuring that the records of customers remittance were processed swiftly and accurately.

2016 - 2017 IT staff(Independent National Electoral Commission, Abuja, Nigeria)

- Functional as a logistics and procurement officer with the responsibility of taking stock inventory of purchased electoral materials.
- Verified that materials used in the different polling units were properly registered assigned approved by the electoral body.

2013 - 2016 Human Resource Manager(BI AND SONS GUINNESS DEPOT, ABUJA, NIGERIA)

- Supervised staff and monitored the efficiency of staff members using various performance trackers.
- Prepared payroll and issued disciplinary notification to staff breaching the company's code of conduct.
- Worked closely with the health and safety team to provide employees the necessary assessments for a safe working environment.

Interests

Reading non-fiction books, solving puzzles, and socializing with friends and family. Engage a lot in research and broadening my knowledge as well as surfing the web and keeping abreast with technologies